Oh [music] Jesus,
savior,
master, [music]
creator.
[singing] You're the alpha. [music]
Omega,
you're the king of kings. [music]
Hey there, my friends. It's Tom with
Watchman River. I am so glad you're here
and I hope you're doing well. Today is
Wednesday, September 2nd, 2026. It is a
lovely day here in the middle of
Connecticut by the river. And as far as
a a live studio audience today, Misty
the Cat, who has been missing in action
for quite a while, she was back today a
few minutes ago, but she has left and
she looked fine. So, some people were
worried about her. She's doing fine. Uh
there are a few birds across the street
on the fence. So that qualifies as
today's live studio audience. And before
we get into our message today, it's
always important, I believe, to start
off in the word of God. So I'm going to
read one of my favorite psalms. And I
know a lot of you love this one, too.
Let's go to Psalm 100. Okay.
Make a joyful shout to the Lord, all you
lands. Serve the Lord with gladness.
Come before his presence with singing.
Know that the Lord, he is God. It is he
who made us and not we ourselves. We are
his people and the sheep of his pasture.
Enter into his gates with thanksgiving
and into his courts with praise. Be
thankful to him and bless his name. For
the Lord is good. His mercy is
everlasting
and his truth endures to all
generations. Oh, give me an amen.
Thank you. I heard that. I heard it. All
right. So, today I have so much to cover
and you got to stay tuned for the Clown
World segment because we're going to
share a couple videos there. And if
you're listening to this as a podcast,
as an audio only podcast, I will give
you a blowby-blow so you know what's
going on. But there's just so much in
this world that is just showing us the
times we are in. We are waiting for
Jesus now, not 10 years down the road. I
happen to believe the pre-tribulation
rapture could happen at any time. We are
in the season. We are late in the season
and we are waiting for Jesus. I don't
know the day or the hour. Nobody does.
I'll tell you one thing though. It's
getting close. It's getting close. But
we have to start off here. Listen to
this. Futurism shared this
alarming study suggests that using AI is
turning humans more robotic. Whoa.
Now that AI models have officially
passed the touring test, there's no
doubt that they're capable of imitating
human traits, at least in text form, to
a degree that would have flabbergasted
even an expert just a couple years back.
After all, large language models are
built by digesting copious amounts of
human authored content, making them
little more than algorithms that mirror
our behavior back at us. Yeah, we've
seen that. Uh, but the more we use AI
tools like OpenAI's chat GPT or
Anthropics Claude, those tables are
starting to turn. Chatbots appear to be
influencing human behavior, making us
behave more like them. A terrifying
thought as the tech plays an ever
greater role in our lives. What are we
reading? We are more like the We're
turning into the robots. [music]
I just we're living in the Twilight
Zone. Let's continue.
As detailed in a new paper in the
journal AI and Society, designed to
build out a new framework and start a
discussion, an international team of
researchers, have suggested that the use
of AI chatbots, specifically in customer
service settings, could be making humans
act more robotic even as bots become
more like us.
Okay. As generative systems and socially
responsive service agents enter everyday
consumption, human AI interaction
increasingly resembles a quasi social
encounter rather than a utilitarian
interface. The report wrote, "The
researchers introduced a new concept.
Listen to this. A new concept called
robbotoid humanness to put a name to the
emergent drift in which consumers come
to experience themselves as most fluent,
correct, or socially viable when they
become compatible with machine
legibility,
machine pacing, and machine logic."
That's incredible. Robbotoid humanness.
Let's just call it Robbotoiletry
humanopoulos. All right, just for humor
sake. Okay, robbotoiletry humanopoulos.
But that's the new term.
Put differently, this is a birectional
influence where robots become more like
people and people become more like
robots. Oh Lord Jesus, please come get
us soon. I am ready to step off of clown
world here and I know most of you are as
we wait for him. But you know, imitation
is the sincerest form of flattery. So,
thank you robots for wanting to be like
us and and we want to be like you now. I
guess I don't, but somebody does.
[laughter] It's not me. But are you
seeing what's going on in this world in
the last days? How much longer can this
go on? Is this sustainable? Do you think
we're living in a sustainable world? I
don't happen to think so. I think we're
in the last days. You know, I don't
think the rapture is in in 50 years. I
think we're looking now and I think most
of you know that we're looking now.
Crazy. Let's go to some news that's
going on in the world. So yesterday
once again, US forces launched strikes
Tuesday against Iran's revolutionary
guards in response to attempted attacks
on commercial shipping and American
forces. The US military said this was
about noon time our um New York City
time yesterday these attacks started. I
just called it Tuesday because they seem
to be happening all the time. But
they're back to attacking Iran and of
course Iran is responding. But Insider
Paper said President Trump warned Iran
yesterday on Tuesday not to retaliate
against the latest US strikes, saying
that Tran faced much harder and higher
attacks if it hits back. So much harder
and higher attacks if it hits back,
which it started to last night. Trump
said Tuesday's US attacks near the
straight of Hormuz were in response to
Iran laying these mines and shooting
missiles at an American base in Jordan.
Quote, "If the failed nation of Iran
retaliates for this very justified
attack, they will be hit again and at a
much harder and higher level. But it
will not be the biggest attack of them
all. All that is waiting in the wings.
and when it is over, there will be very
little left of the Islamic Republic of
Iran." End of quote. That's what
President Trump said on his true social
network. So, we are once again
experiencing this and I really believe
at some point this is going to blow up,
you know, and it looks like it could
happen at any time, but it's not. We're
going we're not going in the direction
of peace. I don't believe and I hate
war, but I think we're going in the
direction of major prophetic wars
ramping up.
So then Iran says it will respond to US
attacks despite President Trump's
threats. And it said, quote, "The United
States will regret its new attacks."
There you go.
Iran targeted Marine barracks in Jordan.
They sent drones on Bahrain and Kuwait
after Trump's new strikes. So they did
respond last night.
Um, Jordan's military said its defenses
intercepted 10 of the 13 missiles while
the remaining three exploded in areas
that were far from population centers
and there were no casualties among
forces stationed there. Now, Iran said
differently. They said that there were
casualties, American casualties, but I
don't know the bottom line of that yet.
Time will tell. Iranian officials said
Wednesday that a US strike hit a wedding
party in the country's south, claiming
more than 50 people were killed or
wounded as fighting in the Middle East
ramps back up. A US military spokesman
said central command was aware of the
reports and that the US military never
targets civilians. So, I don't know what
happened there. It definitely did
happen. Some people are saying it's the
United States. Some people are saying it
was an errant missile from Iran. And we
won't know for a little while. Time
always seems to iron everything out and
you know we get to know after a mount of
time. But pray for the families there
because the people in Iran are different
than the regime in Iran.
Iran's IRGC claims it struck a US base
in Jordan with ballistic missiles,
killing a large number of US forces.
That's what they're saying. Again, I
don't see the verification of that as of
yet. Okay. US forces intercepted Iranian
attacks according to Al Jazera and Iran
says it targeted US military base in
Bahrain.
Uh US officials says Iranian attacks on
Jordan caused no major damage and
Kuwait's air defenses activated
following the Iranian missile and drone
attack. So it was popping off last night
once again and then it all went quiet
for a while and we'll see where it goes
today.
You guys okay? Everybody okay? You might
want to pause the video now and go get
us a snack. Okay, I could use a snack. I
know you could. I'm in the mood lately.
You guys know I love like peanuts in the
shell salted. That That's what I like. I
actually got a couple bags from Texas
Roadhouse recently. I love those. I love
those peanuts. But you get what you want
and then come back. Okay. All right.
This is an Oh, the lawn mower guys are
here. Wonderful. So, you're going to
hear a lot of lawnmowing going on. Uh,
this is from Insider Paper. Iran's
security chief says the US to face new
war strategy after strikes. You will
soon see that Iran's new strategy on the
battlefield, in diplomacy, and in
confronting the economic blockade will
shatter your foundations.
Sorry, I just I had to do that.
Dramatic. It that was dramatic. No, I I
thought that sounded dramatic.
Anyway, that's what the Supreme National
Security Council Secretary uh Raz posted
that on Acts, that little dramatic
threat there. And what are you gonna do?
It's going to shatter our foundations.
I'm waiting for Jesus. You know, he's my
foundation.
Then we got this. Listen to the two
sides of this coin. Russia says what is
happening in the Gulf region is horrific
and they are trying to deescalate recent
actions regarding Iran.
But at the same time, a major new report
yesterday revealed that Russia has
reportedly been quietly assisting Iran
with one of Thran's most ambitious
weapon programs, the development of
advanced supersonic cruise missiles
capable of threatening US aircraft
carriers and other warships throughout
the Middle East. So Russia's like,
"We're mortified. We just can't believe
what's going on in Iran." while they're
also helping them with their arms, you
know. But anybody surprised? I'm not
surprised. Are you surprised? I'm not.
Then we got this from Insider Paper. A
top Iranian official called on citizens
to curb their petrol consumption on
Tuesday as the country faces difficulty
importing enough fuel to meet the demand
due to this US naval blockade. quote,
"Of course, part of the responsibility
for this high consumption does not lie
with our people. It lies with our
industry." End of quote. That's what
parliamentary speaker uh Galibbof said
in a televised address. So, they're
telling them to watch it with the fuel.
You know, go low on the fuel and and the
last quote was, "But in any case, what
is clear is that we need to save
gasoline in our consumption."
So, it really does appear that this is
[music] squeezing them and and working.
Oh, I love lawnmowers. I love
lawnmowers. All right, let me just stay
on task here, Tom. Don't look at the
lawnmowers.
This is from Insider Paper. Chinese
President Xiinping told his Egyptian
counterpart on Wednesday that quote,
"External interference in the Middle
East should be opposed," Beijing state
media reported following talks in Cairo
between the two leaders.
quote, "We must uphold the principle
that the people of the Middle East are
the masters of their own affairs. Oppose
external interference." He's he's
talking about the USA there. And support
regional countries in strengthening
dialogue on peace and security. He had
to end it with those three words because
they everything's ending with peace and
security the last couple years. But
there you go. You know, then we got this
from insider paper. US Treasury
Secretary Bessent or Bessant, I believe
it's Bessant, said the straight of
Hormuz will be bypassed in two years and
will become a worthless piece of water.
He also said this. He said, I will say
it on worldwide TV. We know where in the
British Virgin Islands your accounts
are. He's talking to Iran.
At these trust companies, we know the
hundred million dollar houses you have
around the world. We are going to close
all that down. We are going after the
regime's assets they have stolen from
the Iranian people. They can go instead
to the victims of terror. After 47
years, it is over. Either you are with
us or against us. End of quote. So,
they're pretty serious about these
economic sanctions. I don't think Iran
cares. I think they care, but it's not
going to they're not going to wave the
surrender flag, especially when they
got, you know, China and Russia doing
all these backend things that, you know,
they're they're just not going to
surrender. I think most of us know that.
Then we got this. Overnight last night,
the Hezbollah terrorist organization
launched two explosive drones toward IDF
soldiers in the area of the Ali El
Tahare Ridge. That's in southern
Lebanon. IDF soldiers opened fire and
downed one of the drones. There were no
injuries reported. In response to this
attack, the IDF struck Hezbollah terror
infrastructure in the area of Nabatia in
southern Lebanon. So, you know what that
means? It's Wednesday. It's just, you
know, it just happens every day.
Then we got this. I got this from from
Rapture Ready.
Chinese student charged with lying to
border agents over alleged airport photo
assignments from Beijing.
A Chinese national studying at a
Canadian university has been charged
with lying to American officials to
conceal that he took photographs at a
Chicago airport cargo facility at the
direction of a suspected Chinese
official. According to a federal
complaint filed in Detroit on August
26th.
Incredible.
What else you've heard about? Have you
heard about this? This is just
Google's plan to release 32 million
labraised mosquitoes. What are the
risks? I found this on rapture
ready.com. Google owned Debug has
proposed releasing 32 million Wbakia
infected male mosquitoes in California
and Florida to suppress populations of
an invasive mosquito that spreads the
deni fever and the yellow fever and the
Zika virus. Public concern centers on
unintended
environmental consequences, the
difficulty of reversing largecale
biological releases and the role of
private corporations in ecosystem
management. Yeah, I think there would be
public concerns. you know, they they
build these little mosquitoes and they
alter these little mosquitoes and then
they release them, you know, and we're
supposed to say, "Great." You know,
meanwhile, we're going to find out that,
you know, well, I can't say that in a
YouTube video, but we're going to find
out they're carrying something. I'll
just say, you know, who knows? I don't
worry about this stuff because I belong
to the King of Kings and the Lord of
Lords, and most of you do, too. And I
know that Jesus isn't rattled at all by
anything going on in this crazy world.
and I trust him and I know that we are
in the last days and I'm just not
troubled by this stuff. Earthquakes the
last 24 hours went up a little bit.
There were 64 over 4.0 and 29 over 5.0.
So, they went up a little bit. There you
go.
Okay, it's time for the question of the
day. We started this a couple days ago,
the question of the day, and uh it's
really going well. I'm really enjoying
all the stuff I'm seeing in the comments
from it. So, let's do it.
Question [music] of the day. What's your
favorite rapture verse in the Bible?
That's my question of the day. We all
have our favorites. I I love rapture
verses. I think you know that. And I
think there's many more than people even
realize, you know, but what's your
favorite one? Now, I'm going to tell you
my favorite one, but honestly, if you
ask me tomorrow, it might switch. But
I'm going to say John 14:3. Okay? And if
I go and prepare a place for you, I will
come again and receive you unto myself
that where I am, there you may be also.
The words of Jesus. That's mine for
today, you know. So, what's your
favorite rapture verse? Let me know.
Okay. All right. All right, you guys.
It's time for clown world. Get ready.
Get ready for this.
A driverless car hits a police van after
the internet goes down during a Pakistan
demo. So, let's roll the video here.
He's driving this self-driv the
passengers just sitting there. You can
see the wheels spinning and look what
they're heading toward. The only car in
the area, a police car. And wab boommy,
[laughter]
it hit the police car. Incred. Let's
watch it one more time. Okay, look. The
only car in the area. And the look at
he's aiming for it. the self-driving car
is aiming for it. I love the way the guy
reaches down to pull the handbrake when
he realizes, look, he's like, "Whoa, got
to pull the handbrake." And that might
have lessened the impact a little bit,
but there you go. That is total and
complete clown world. That's why. And
and I love the way the story says after
the internet goes down. See, we're
relying on the internet to run all these
things. And when the internet glitches,
the police car gets hit. You know,
that's clown world.
It's just clown world. All right, I got
another one. I got another one. This
Russian robot tries to attack a customer
after he pushed it. So, check out this
video. You got the robot. You got the
guy shaking hands with the robot.
The robot gets angry because the guy
pushes him a little bit. Watch what the
robot does. Does he just calmly? No. No.
So, he gets in position and he is ready
to whoop.
[laughter]
Another guy comes out. They're fighting
with a robot. The robot's trying to get
that guy. Watch what the robot's foot
does on the top of the desk there. Wait
till you see this. He's like stumbling
and fl. Whoa. [laughter]
Oh, come on. That's good. That's good.
No, I I like that. I like that. One more
time. Okay. One more time.
There we go. There we go. clown world.
We are living in clown
world with all these robots and
self-driving cars and the flying cars
are coming. They're coming very soon and
so is Jesus. Thank God. Uh so we're
waiting. But let's read a few comments
of the day. Okay.
So yesterday's question of the day was
beside Jesus, who are you most excited
to see in heaven? And um I'm going to
tell you that
there were many that I could never read
on these videos cuz I will cry. You
know, there were many. So I tried to
pick ones that hopefully won't make me
cry. Okay. But um you know, I said I was
excited to see my mom and dad, you know,
and there was a lot of people saying
that, but some of them are just, you
know, but Sarah said, "I'm excited to be
reunited with my daughter. I just
wonder, will she be the same age when
she passed or will she be what she would
have been before going home to the Lord?
Either way, it will be a wonderful
reunion. Amen, sister. Amen. Oh, can you
imagine?
We're in heaven. I don't know if I can
talk about this. Can you imagine we're
in heaven and we see those reunions of
people that lost babies
and we literally see those reunions? I
just
All right. Um,
all right.
Matthew said
he's most looking forward to seeing my
brother Aaron. He was killed
in action in Afghanistan on November
5th, 2009.
And there hasn't been a day since that I
have not missed him.
these were the ones that weren't
supposed to make me struggle.
All right. Um, Mrs. Manners,
who am I most excited to see? Well,
since we have eternity and I believe
that time will be different, so I want
to see Daniel. There are no words. I
have a burning desire to see Daniel and
hear what he experienced. Knowing that
we will see our loved ones who went
before us is more than I can even
imagine. Amen, sister. Amen. And yeah,
Daniel talking to Daniel and you know
Paul and I just can't wait. We have an
amazing future if you know Jesus.
Rick, no fear here. I know without a
doubt that Jesus is coming for us at the
perfect moment and I couldn't care less
about AI. Awesome, brother. Thank you,
Rick. Beautiful. Let's do one more
gospel festival. Brother Tom, I am with
you. What world are we living in? But we
are not worried because we have a
wedding to attend. Marinatha. Amen.
Thank you for that. Amen. We do. We do.
Jesus is coming soon and he is going to
receive us to himself that where he is
there we may be also. But do you know
Jesus? Do you have a relationship with
him? Do you believe in the gospel?
Because that's how you're saved, by
believing in the gospel. That means good
news. Well, what's the good news? Well,
here it is. We're all sinners. We all
fall short of the glory of God. We're
not perfect, right? Everyone agree to
that? Of course, we're far from perfect.
And Jesus came here from heaven 2,000
years ago to to save us, to rescue us,
to take our sins. And when we sin, all
of our sins were placed on Jesus when he
was on the cross. And in exchange, he
gives us his righteousness. But he paid
for every one of our sins, past,
present, and future on that cross. You
know, so many people beat themselves up
over past sins. You know, I did this
thing. I just don't know if I'll ever be
forgiven. You're you're saying that
Jesus going to a bloody cross wasn't
enough. that your sin is so special, you
need some kind of extra payment. It's
not right, guys. Don't do that. I did
that for years. Don't do that. Jesus
paid for all of our sins. He took every
sin that has ever been committed on him.
And in exchange, once you believe in the
atoning blood and in the finished work
of Jesus, we get his righteousness. And
the most high God doesn't even remember
our sins. Satan will always remind you
because Satan doesn't want you to get to
the point where you say, "All of my sins
are gone because Jesus paid for them
with his blood." Satan doesn't want you
to get to that point because you'll have
a great walk with Jesus. But I guarantee
you, if you let Satan continue to remind
you over and over and over again about
your past sins, you're not going to have
a good walk with Jesus. It's not a
salvation issue. Your sins were paid for
by the blood of the lamb, Jesus. But
it's hard to walk with Jesus when you're
falling for Satan's. Let me remind you
what you did. You tell him, "You know
what? I know what Jesus did and it is
done." Jesus said, "It is finished."
When he was on the cross, he paid for
all of our sins with his blood. It is
finished.
So, how do you get saved? How do you
know you're saved? You get alone with
Jesus. And you have to understand you're
a sinner who needs payment for your sin.
And if you say to Jesus, "Jesus, I I
believe that you shed that blood to wash
me white as snow to get rid of my sin
problem. I believe in your atoning blood
and I have faith in your finished work.
I know you were nailed to the cross and
you shed that precious blood and you
died and you were buried and you rose
again the third day. And I need a
savior, Jesus. And I now realize you're
the one and only savior of the world
because he is. That is why everyone is
so against him in this world." and you
say, "Jesus, I I believe in you now.
Your atoning blood, your finished work,
the gospel, the good news." And at that
moment of belief, you are saved. You're
sealed until the day of redemption. He
won't let you out of the palm of his
hand.
Please, please, please understand the
simplicity of the gospel.
It's so important. If this sounds like
truth to you, if you're like, you know
what, this sounds like truth, run to
Jesus now and talk to him because today
could be your day. Today could be the
day that you look back on for the rest
of eternity and say, "That day is the
day when I finally said, "Oh, Jesus,
take these sins. I know you washed them
away with your blood. I don't want to
think about them. Change me. I believe
in your gospel, your good news, and get
saved today. Today is the day of
salvation." Okay? You don't want to put
this off because if you're thinking,
"Well, I don't know if I believe this or
not." you walk away from this and you
never believe in Jesus atoning blood and
finished work. You're going to face him
on judgment day and that is a nightmare.
He's going to say, "Away from me, I
never knew you." You're going to end up
eternally separated from God. And you're
not going to say, "This is not fair."
You're going to say, "You're a fair and
just God because you've heard this
gospel message. You heard about the
rescue plan that Jesus did."
Okay? You heard it now. You are without
excuse. Your sins were paid for by the
blood of the lamb of God. By the blood
of Jesus, they were paid for.
All right. In my prayer time this
morning, I said a prayer for every
single person who would watch this
video. So, you have been prayed for
today. And if we're not raptured today,
and you know, I think today's a
perfectly good day, but it's not up to
me. But if not today, God willing, I
will see you guys tomorrow. I love you
guys.
>> Oh, Jesus.
Savior, [music]
master,
creator.
[music] You're the alpha.
Omega,
you're [music] the king of kings.